Finding Aid for Jeep Holland papers, 1943-1998
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Sound Recordings
  - Mr. Curt, "Write Down Your Number," (B side; "I'm Going Blind"), 1978; 1 phonograph records 45rpm (Box 10)
  - Ray Paul, "Lady Be Mine Tonight," (B side; "Hold It"), 1977; 1 phonograph records 45rpm (Box 10)
  - Plain Brown Wrapper, "Stretch Out Your Hand," (B side; "Stretch Out Your Hand (2)"), 1 phonograph records 45rpm (Box 10)
  - Rain like the Sound of Trains, "Bad Man's Grave," (B side; "Cookin With Anger"), 1993; 1 phonograph records 45rpm (Box 10)
  - The UP, "Just Like and Aborigine," (B side; "Hassan I Sabbah"), 1970; 1 phonograph records 45rpm (Box 10)
  - Miscellaneous, 2 phonograph records 45rpm
    - "A Hard Days Night before Christmas" (Box 10)
    - "Kocaine Karma" (Box 10)
- Visual
  Visual (1943-1998, 2.25 linear feet) consists of visual resources such as photographs of Jeep, photographs of Jeep's friends, photos from Jeep's childhood, and photos of various A-Square, Universal Artists, and Diamond Comics personalities and functions. The series also contains scrapbooks detailing Jeep's childhood, and one of the bands he worked with, The Rationals. In addition, there is one outsize box containing an unbound scrapbook concerning The Rationals, three concert posters, and one large portrait of Jeep from when he was in high school.
  - Laminated Newspaper Clippings (Box 10)
  - Photographs
    - Gibb, Russ (Box 10)
    - High School Friends (Box 10)
    - Jeep photographs
      - Assorted photos
        - 1960s-1970s (Box 10)
        - 1970s-1980s (Box 10)
        - 1980s-1990s (Box 10)
      - Jeep with celebrities (Box 10)
      - Childhood (Box 10)
      - Memorial (Box 11)
        - Gathering, 1998 (Box 11)
        - Young Jeep album (Box 11)
    - Laminated photos
      - Large (Box 11)
      - Small (Box 11)
    - Marsha (Box 11)
    - Miscellaneous
      - late 1960s-early 1970s (Box 11)
      - 1970s-1980s (Box 11)
      - 1980s-1990s (Box 11)
    - Perrine, Pep (Box 11)
    - Proof Sheets (Box 11)
    - Slides (Box 11)
    - Tiboni, Joe (Box 11)
  - Scrapbooks
    - California, 1958
      - Autographs (Box 11)
      - Brochures (Box 11)
      - Disneyland (Box 11)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 11)
      - Photographs
        - Beach/High school friends (Box 11)
        - Disneyland (Box 11)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 11)
        - Sight seeing (Box 11)
      - Ticket stubs (Box 11)
    - Childhood
      - Photographs
        - Boy Scout camp/vacation (Box 11)
        - Camp Al Gon Quian
          - Large (Box 11)
          - Small (Box 11)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 11)
    - Rationals Unofficial Scrapbook
      - Concert flyers (Box 11)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 11)
      - Newspaper clippings (Box 11)
      - Photographs
        - Large (Box 11)
        - Small (Box 11)
      - Photograph collage (Box 11)
      - Radio charts, 1966-1968 (Box 11)
    - Snapshots, 1943-1945 (Box 11)
    - Diamond Comics, "The Diamond Way" (Box 12)
    - The Rationals, "In the Beginning" (Box 12)
    - The Rationals scrapbook (Box 13)
  - Other Visual Materials
    - Concert Posters, 3 posters (Box 13)
    - Jeep portrait (Box 13)